TENZIN KUNCHOK

Full Stack Developer

+31 638947645 @ tenzinkunchok@tibet.dev

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tenzin-kunchok-669592240/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with experience in modern JavaScript. For me, web development is more than just writing code. Is to communicate and work well with others in a team and to be curious and open to criticism and different approaches, to solve problems, telling stories thought visual representation and to continue doing what I love, in a challenging but friendly environment

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (Volunteer)

2022 - Present

Tibetan Community Netherlands

Amsterdam

The Tibetan Community Netherlands aids Tibetans in establishing new lives. Founded in 2005, it promotes unity, guided by non-sectarian principles. Elected leaders follow Dalai Lama's teachings and Central Tibetan Administration directives.

- Developed a contemporary website with a blend of modern aesthetics and cultural essence. https://tibetcommunity.nl
- Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Full Stack Developer

10/2023 - Present

HackYourFuture

Amsterdam

Coding school offering an intense seven months course thought by professional developers. Curriculum includes modules in HTML, CSS, GitHub, JavaScript, Node, MySQL, MongoDB and React, Problem-solving skills and teamwork are additional parts of the curriculum. Throughout the course as always I continued learning and exploring extra new skills and technology such as TypeScript, EditorJs, CKEditor, Firebase etc.

Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Graphic Designer

2021 - 03/2022

Private Individual

Preserving ancient Tibetan Buddhist handwritten manuscripts through digital restoration using Photoshop and InDesign, followed by publishing the enhanced versions for public access

More than 1000s of pages restored

Freelance Developer

2020 - Present

Location

Private Individuals Company Description

· Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

ACHIEVEMENTS

Tibetan Community Netherlands Website

Created a fully functional and visually appealing website for the Tibetan Community in the Netherlands.

Founder and Manger, Tibet.Dev

Pioneering the Tibetan Developers' Community, facilitating occasional gatherings for knowledge sharing and fostering connections among members.

First Tibetan to be part of HYF program.

Why are you proud of this achievement?



SKILLS

TypeScript · JavaScript · NodeJS · React ·

ExpressJs · HTML5 · Css3 · Sass ·

MySQL · MongoDB · Git · GitHub ·

Wordpress · Figma · Boot Strap ·

Chakra UI · Firebase · Vite · Netlify ·

Adobe Photoshop · Adobe Illustrator ·

Editor.Is

Tool / Technology

EDUCATION

Learning Every Day

Open Source

2019 - Present

Full Stack Developer

HackYourFuture

2022 - 07/2024

Dutch Language

Hogeschool van Amsterdam

11/2022 - 06/2024

Tibetan Buddhist Philosophy

Summer Buddhis school

2000 - 2012

LANGUAGES

Tibetan	Native	•••••
English	Proficient	••••
Dutch	Advanced	••••
Hindi	Advanced	••••
Chinese	Intermediate	••••

